你可是个超级歌星啊
I mean, you are a huge singing star,
我却要用声音震撼你
And here I am trying to impress you with my voice.
卡尔 我就是个平凡的老家伙 行吗?
Kyle, now, I'm just a regular old guy, all right?
我没什么特别的
Nothing special about me, okay?
好吧 好吧 我将要唱的是...
Okay, okay, well, what I was gonna sing is...
我是说 我是独特
I mean, I was special.
当我在演唱时候 你可以想象下
I mean, when you think about it, when I was singing, you know?
爷可是和迈克.麦当劳合唱过的 懂吗?
When I did that duet with michael McDonald, you know?
你懂的
you know?
是的 - 但是
Yeah. - But, yeah.
那个的确特别 不过这跟我没关系
That was special, you know? But it's not about me.
这是你的时刻 你要为我们演唱什么?
This is about you. So what you got for us?
好的 我带来
Okay, so here goes:
奇异盛典
amazing grace
谢谢 - 怎么了?
Thank you. - What?
卡尔 跑调太明显了 太跑了
Kyle, that was real pitchy, dog, real pitchy.
你懂的 - 你走把
You know... - Off you go.
那我唱另外首 - 可以了
Well, I got another song... - You're done.
我们会联系你的 - 才怪
We'll call you. - We won't.
老兄 这就是我们的好苗子?
Man, is that the best we got?
是的 我们得坚信
Yes, and we have to let the judges know.
潜力股正在出现
Our lead singer right away.
时间所剩无几了 -闹心
The clock is ticking, reverend. Dang it.
我都在集会上宣布
I mean, I told the whole congregation.
我们会赢了
We were gonna win this thing,
但现在我还没看见一个有才的
And I don't think we got anybody good enough.
你可别忘了你是目视着众人的眼睛
And don't forget you looked them in the eye.
对他们保证过的
And gave them the boyce ballentine guarantee.
我知道我有
I know what I did.
还有最后两个了
Well, there are two more auditions,
看来也是没戏了 算了吧 -别这样
But it's probably not worth it. Oh, don't do that.
还是看看 说不定有奇迹呢
Let's see them, all right? They... they could be great.
你硬要的话
If you insist.
下一个
Next!
哦
Oh
我爱耶稣
How I love jesus
哦
Oh
我爱耶稣
How I love jesus
哦
Oh
为什么我爱耶稣
How I love jesus
因为他先无私的爱着我
Because he first loved me
耶! 这样才像话嘛!
Yeah! Now that's what I'm talking about!
你还说不见他们呢
And you didn't even want to see them.
我兄啊
My bad.
女士们 你叫什么
Ladies, what's your names?
- 我叫露丝 - 我交凯瑟琳
- I'm rose. - And I'm catherine.
我们是粉红姐妹
And we're the pinkney sisters.
你会招她们的 是吗
You just had to bring them, didn't you?
你还想不想要赢啊
Do you want to win, or not?
你知道这对我们教堂意味着什么吗
Do you know what this would mean to our church?
我当然知道
Of course I do.
但 不 不
But... No, no, no.
不 这不行 我不能这么做
No, this is wrong. I can't do it.
因为开销问题
We could pay them out of petty cash.
她们可是摇钱树啊
That way, we won't leave a paper trail.
哦
Oh
我爱耶稣
how I love jesus
因为耶稣
Because he first
博爱人间
Loved me
招吧
Do it.
亲爱的 今天可是我在沙龙过的最好的一天
Baby, today was the best day ever at the salon.
起来 我要让你爽死
Stand up so I can make it rain on you.
现在没心情 宝贝
I'm not in the mood, babe.
怎么了
What's wrong?
我感觉不太好
You know, I just don't feel good.
雇佣了那两个女孩
About hiring those ringers.
我想你是太过于担心了
I think you're being too hard on yourself.
就把它当成是比投资啊
You know, just think of it as making an investment.
为教堂的未来着想啊
In the future of your church.
我要是你 我就这么想
I mean, that's what I thought, you know?
我真的很想赢
And I do want to win this thing.
好吧 有时我们要学会知足
Well, sometimes we got to do what we got to do.
你说的没错
I guess you're right.
好把 谢谢宝贝
All right, thank you, baby.
你没有留下活动记录吧
You didn't leave a paper trail, did you?
你好 老妈
Hey, mom.
我朋友的妈妈说
So my friend's mother said.
Stamps已经做了两星期了
That stamps is booked up for two whole weeks.
她出五十刀叫我给她
She offered to give me 50 bucks if I can get them in.
Lyric 我不会要那五十刀的
Lyric, I would never take 50 bucks.
就为那点小事
For something like that.
如果你能找来七十五个 再来谈谈
Now if you can get the lady up to 75, come talk to me.
我尽力而为
I'll see what I can do.
有小费吗
Do I get a cut?
如果你找来七十五个 我给你十五刀
If you get 75, I'll give you 15.
那要是八十个 能有二十刀吗
What if I get you 80? Can I get 20?
知女莫若母啊
My baby!
你们俩搞什么呢
What is going on with you two?
没什么
Nothing.
我正在谈生意呢
I'm just doing what's best for my business.
就想你在为教堂拼死拼活一样样的
Like you're doing what's best for the church.
我不禁想起
You know, I just can't help but feel.
我们都在铤而走险
We both made a deal with the devil.
我不认为我是哦
Well, I don't think I did.
嗨 老板娘 我的支票簿呢
Hey, boss lady. You got my paycheck?
-就在这儿 - 好的
- Right here. - All right.
你又要去哪里鬼混啊
Where are you going all slicked up, slick?
我有个约会
I got a date.
我可要好好的约会哦
I met a little something-something today.
哇 哇 不要 告诉我
Whoa, whoa, whoa. Please don't tell me.
你在和我的顾客约会
You're dating one of my customers.
我同意 但我不会告诉你的
Yeah, I agree. I shouldn't tell you about it.
- Stamps - 别担心 老娘
- Stamps. - Don't worry, boss.
这对生意后好处 相信我
This will be good for business, trust me.
这叫 顾客关系
I call it "customer relations."
只是出去吃吃 喝喝
So I'm just gonna head out and go... Relate.
老天啊 我也许是在铤而走险
Oh, my god, maybe I did make a deal with the devil.
这样看来
And in that case,
还会赚到黑心钱
That would make this the devil's money.
你不要 我要哦
You want me to take that off your hands?
休想
No.
你要我霸王硬上弓吗?
Oh, you want to play "rob the bank."